dbr.ee 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy - DBREE

Last updated: March 10, 2016

DBREE ("us", "we", or "our") operates [https://dbr.ee](https://dbr.ee/) (the "Site") (collectively, the “Service”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of collected information we receive from users of the Service. 

## Information Collection And Use

While using our Service, you may have provided us with information. We collect information when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the Service, fill out a form, make a purchase, communicate with us via social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number, credit card information and any other information you choose to provide. Our servers automatically collect certain technical information (“Technical Data”) about your use of the Service. Technical Data is collected as follows: 

  * Log Information: Our servers automatically recognize and log visitors' IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet), Internet service provider, browser type, computer platform, referring web site, date and time of access, links clicked through, and possibly other information as well. 
  * Cookies: We may use the standard "cookies" feature of major browser applications or similar technologies such as HTML 5 local storage that allow us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Service. Some of the cookies we use are associated with your account (including personal information about you, such as the email address you gave us), and other cookies are not. Advertisers may also use cookies on our Service. We have no access to or control over these cookies once our third-party advertisers have been given permission to set cookies. This Policy only covers use of cookies by us, and does not cover use of cookies by any third-party advertiser. 
  * Location: We may collect information about the location of your device each time you access or use one of our mobile applications or otherwise consent to the collection of this information. 
  * Other Device: We collect information about the computer device you use to access our Service, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information. 
  * Account Information: This may include, without limitation, your username, password, email address, profile photo or avatar, biographic information, comments, and any other information you may provide to us when you sign up or as you use the Service. When you use a third-party service, like Facebook or Twitter, to create and authenticate an account, you also agree to their terms of service, privacy policy, and other agreements between you and them. 

## Use of Information

We may also use your information as follows:

  * Account Information. We may use your personal information to verify your identity or to help your friends find you on the Service. We may also use your contact information to respond to your questions or comments, to inform you of any changes to our Service, to send you additional information about the Service, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 
  * Technical Data. We use anonymous Technical Data to analyze our website traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our Service, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and Site activity information may also be shared with advertisers and other third parties on an aggregate and anonymous basis. 
  * Cookies. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to remember you when you return to the Service, or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our Service may also contain cookies (or technologies with similar function). We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our Service. 

## Sharing of Information

When you post content to the Service, your content becomes public and anyone can view it. We may disclose other information about you or your use of the Service, which may include Technical Data and/or Account Information, under certain appropriate circumstances, such as: 

  * With your consent; 
  * When we have a good-faith belief that we must in order to comply with the law or with legal process served on us or our affiliates, 
  * When necessary to protect and defend our rights or property, or those of our users, or to act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of our users or the public at large; or 
  * To facilitate a sale of the Service or a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this Policy. 

## Your Choices

You have various choices about your information on the Service:

  * You can post content to the Service without signing up for an account, in which case we only collect Technical Data and Device Data from you. 
  * When you do create an account with us, you can access and edit your profile at any time accessing the Settings page when logged in. 
  * You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Service may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended. 
  * You may disable the collection of GPS information by altering your device settings so that location information is no longer made available, but if you do so this could negatively affect your experience while using or otherwise accessing the Service. 

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 10, 2016 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. 

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our Service. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#85e6eaebf1e4e6f1c5e1e7f7abe0e0).
